Amanda Chi: Hi!
km Habib: Right.
Amanda Chi: How's your day going so far?
km Habib: Yeah, fine.
km Habib: How's your end?
km Habib: How's going your day?
Amanda Chi: Pretty good, too.
km Habib: Great.
Amanda Chi: Kayla.
Kayla Kanipe: Yay.
km Habib: That's always kind of a funny week, going into, into Thanksgiving, so…
Kayla Kanipe: Wrapping things up, busy, I'm surprised it's not quieter, frankly, Amanda.
Amanda Chi: I know.
Kayla Kanipe: That's okay.
Amanda Chi: We'll see how tomorrow goes, and then Wednesday, too.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah. Exactly.
Kayla Kanipe: Mad dash to get stuff out, you know.
Kayla Kanipe: Out this week, and then for the next couple days.
Kayla Kanipe: I'm excited about this. I didn't prepare for this, but I am prepared, so…
Kayla Kanipe: But I just thought it made sense to bring Amanda to this, and Amanda, if you need to connect with them tomorrow, you can. I just wanted us to be on the same page, since a lot of the stuff in the B4B world
Kayla Kanipe: We have different flows, since we divide and conquer, you know, our work, but we are…
km Habib: It's a problem.
Kayla Kanipe: We're all kind of doing the, you know, we all want to improve these processes, no matter what.
Amanda Chi: Yeah. I have time, actually, on the calendar tomorrow with Matthew, so if you want to just take this, go through most of your things, then I can be here to support or chime in what's relevant, but…
Amanda Chi: Yeah, that way he covers everything that you're doing, for sure.
Matthew smith: Oh, you're here? Perfect.
Kayla Kanipe: How's everyone today?
Kayla Kanipe: Doing well, yeah.
Matthew smith: Good.
Matthew smith: Nice. Well, happy to see all your guys' faces. Hopefully your weekend was good.
Matthew smith: Cool, so just to kind of…
Matthew smith: Set the tone for the meeting.
Matthew smith: We've…
Matthew smith: Pretty much layered out the whole workflow, all the systems that you guys have, and today's meeting is just to kind of flush out details and make sure that we've recorded everything properly.
Matthew smith: Right.
Matthew smith: So… We… I don't know if… I'm gonna let KM take the… the lead on the call.
Matthew smith: But we can start off with kind of just showing you what we have so far with the workflow mapping and the automation.
Matthew smith: That's cool.
Matthew smith: One second… Alright, let me share my screen here.
Matthew smith: Then let me know when you can see it.
Kayla Kanipe: Still loading.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay, we can see your screen.
Matthew smith: Okay, perfect.
Matthew smith: Alright, so we found we can save about 150 to 200 hours across the… Your whole operation.
Matthew smith: The key findings is we have 4 system data entries,
Matthew smith: You know, that means there's… there's data everywhere, it's scattered.
Matthew smith: We have zero tracking for P2P introductions,
Matthew smith: You have 10 to 20 hours spent a week on extracting tasks from emails to notes.
Matthew smith: And obviously, there's a lot of human error with that. So…
Matthew smith: We'll kind of just dive right into…
Matthew smith: the workflow that we have, make sure everything is good or solid here. We went over this with Mac, so we don't have to…
Matthew smith: Take too long on it.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay.
Amanda Chi: I have a quick question, actually, Matthew.
Amanda Chi: Is this the implementation plan for the client ops side?
Matthew smith: So we win.
Matthew smith: We, on the call Friday, we pretty much covered the exec side.
Matthew smith: So we can go over the client as well.
Matthew smith: Today.
Matthew smith: That makes sense to do so.
Kayla Kanipe: What do you mean by going over the client today?
Matthew smith: Like, client work side, like, what do you guys do, the tasks you guys have, all of that, to make sure we kind of get everything fleshed out.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay, cool. Yeah, I just wanted to make sure, because I thought, diving into the plan, I was like, oh wait, we haven't even talked about our side of the business yet. Yes. So, I just wanted to make sure that we were on the same page here about that.
Matthew smith: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
km Habib: Yeah, I think…
km Habib: Yeah, today I think we're going to talk about before business.
km Habib: And I think Kayla is, your role is to…
Kayla Kanipe: Did I… did I lose him? Oh.
Kayla Kanipe: I think you're back. You froze for a second.
km Habib: Yeah, it's a network issue, I think.
km Habib: It's true.
km Habib: I know the before B site is different from exec sites, and basically… You are…
km Habib: And have this monthly pipeline reviews, I think.
km Habib: Alright.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay, and if you wanted?
Matthew smith: If you want to turn off your video because it's, like, cutting in and out, maybe that'll help.
Matthew smith: With, the service?
km Habib: come from?
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Sorry about that, guys.
Kayla Kanipe: No worries.
Amanda Chi: I had it in the morning. It was not very well, too.
Matthew smith: What'd he say?
Amanda Chi: I had a similar problem this morning, so I understand.
Matthew smith: So, yeah, can't live without tech, can't live with it, it feels like.
Kayla Kanipe: Our best friend and worst enemy sometimes.
Matthew smith: Oh, yeah, he's popping off.
Matthew smith: Well, let's just, I guess, just start from top, top to bottom, on your guys' kind of, operations.
km Habib: I'm sorry, there's going to be a technical issue here.
Kayla Kanipe: No worries.
km Habib: So, basically, I want to understand your day-to-day realities so I can find automation that actually help you.
km Habib: Sure.
km Habib: operation.
km Habib: So, can you work… so, can you walk me through your typical week? Like, what takes up most of your time?
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah, and I think that maybe Amanda and I can,
Kayla Kanipe: maybe Amanda and I can, jump in, because we have different parts and flows, or, like, parts of the flow that, that we, that we take over, but feel free to cut me off and dive into certain areas when… whenever helpful, but…
Kayla Kanipe: I would say that most of my days are…
Kayla Kanipe: are clogged up with calls, and this ranges from B2B client calls, calls for our broader exec network growth.
Kayla Kanipe: Internal calls, making sure that things are moving and grooving in the right direction. And then at the end of the day, it's a lot of those follow-ups. So, you know, what are the action items? Who am I assigning who to where?
Kayla Kanipe: Who do I need to follow up with? Who do I need to, you know, kind of email? In addition to that, I spend a lot of my days doing kind of, like, research for network growth, sending out those emails, scheduling those calls, etc.
Kayla Kanipe: Then there's… my day is a lot… or a lot of my day is filled up with facilitating introductions, so…
Kayla Kanipe: We usually have a lot of intro requests per week, which is great news. That's, you know, what we want to happen, but even me just kind of sending out the personalized email to that executive, teeing up the email, tracking it, doing that, that whole process, like, individually it doesn't take that long, but after a while, it… it does take on… it takes a lot of time.
Kayla Kanipe: I do a thing that we call intro policing, which means I look through all of the pending introductions,
Kayla Kanipe: I see, you know, who… who reached out, did that person open the email? Did someone forget to mark the introduction complete? Like, the human error tracking, remind people to follow up, etc.
Kayla Kanipe: And then a lot of, like… not a lot, but before every call, we… I do, like, the prepping the call notes, so I'll go and reference the last call notes, I'll pull intros from Retool into Notion, so it's all in one place, getting just kind of ready for… ready for that.
Kayla Kanipe: That's a lot of my week.
Kayla Kanipe: And I know that there was a lot of Banff-isms, too, so… and Banff-specific, you know, words, so happy to dive deeper into anything.
km Habib: Yep, yep, got it. Thanks.
km Habib: My next question is, what is the most frustrating part of B4BE operations? Basically, why do you think… why do things press or get stuck here, say, in your daily operation?
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah, and I think I'll answer this in a couple different ways. One, and maybe this is just more top of mind right now, but it will become also
Kayla Kanipe: a lot more prominent when we move into the new year is… the…
Kayla Kanipe: The machine, after we bring in, like, a new exec into our network.
Kayla Kanipe: The machine after that, making sure that their profile is created, their notes are tagged appropriately, they're being sent to the right, you know, teams externally, the right partners.
Kayla Kanipe: There's enough visibility across the entire organization on who those people are. I think that is all
Kayla Kanipe: Definitely a word… just riding the car like a Flintstone, and there's no real, like…
Kayla Kanipe: foolproof process for that. And right now, since I'm owning the majority of…
Kayla Kanipe: what that process is, the Tier 3, we call it just our broader network expansion.
Kayla Kanipe: every kind of, like, week, I definitely go back and just manually check, oh, when was this call, when was that? Maybe I'll send them to this person instead of that person. Like, there's just not a foolproof system around it all. Was that helpful, or was that… Yeah.
km Habib: Yeah, there's, that's, give the answers, I think.
km Habib: So, I think, even computer and screen is on, so can you walk me through a recent entry request, start to finish? Like, can you screen share and show me, in container?
Kayla Kanipe: the process that I just explained, in terms of the, kind of, like, broader network growth.
Matthew smith: Okay, I saw Amanda blank, so it's Amanda Blank.
Kayla Kanipe: Hello?
km Habib: Oh, there's a technical glitch here, I'm sorry.
Kayla Kanipe: No, I'm… I got you back now, so I'm happy to share my screen. I just want to confirm which flow you want me to show you.
km Habib: So basically, from sending, mail to, from on… to onboarding the…
Matthew smith: Exactly.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay.
km Habib: Basically, this is a two-bed noise per tracking finding, and basically understanding the current workaround.
km Habib: Okay. And quantified duplicate.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay, I'll start sharing my screen, and I'll walk through the kind of broader network growth machine that we have right now. And it's clunky, so… so bear with me here.
Kayla Kanipe: And Matthew, I'm gonna replace the current share.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay, so there's a bunch of different tools that we use, but this is kind of the…
Kayla Kanipe: I guess maybe we should probably start from pipelines. So, pretty much the flow is…
Kayla Kanipe: we're talking to a B4B client, we're on the phone with them, and then… actually, it looks like this. This is the initial flow. Let's just say we're talking to this B4B client.
Kayla Kanipe: He's like, we need a VP of sales, we need a fintech CFO in New York. We're trying to move away from this, but we do still do reactive outreach to keep our clients happy, and so…
Kayla Kanipe: With this, Amanda and I are taking the call notes, we have to go in and make sure it's all appropriately tagged.
Kayla Kanipe: If it's a monthly call, if it's, you know, what the client is, all that good stuff.
Kayla Kanipe: Then we also manually… Add those to-dos, so what we wrote right here of, like.
Kayla Kanipe: refresh CFO pipeline. I go into here, and I write it on… I write it in here,
Kayla Kanipe: High beam CFO.
Kayla Kanipe: I make this note to myself, and then also high beam sales. Oh, did we lose him?
Matthew smith: This year.
Amanda Chi: I think he just…
Matthew smith: Turned his camera off.
Kayla Kanipe: Great. Okay, high beam sales, so this is kind of, like, this is where Amanda and I track all of our, kind of, action items, and then we do, like, all of these.
Kayla Kanipe: Peloton Deputy CISO, Peloton Marketing, Trellis, Strategic Finance, like, I have to go kind of find those people. We're not recruiters, but we kind of are recruiters in a way. So then I use Juicebox, I find all the people, it looks something like this.
Kayla Kanipe: I do all the shortlist, I poll all these people,
Kayla Kanipe: So I probably spend, I don't know, an hour doing research for each specific initiative, and then I go, I pull, pull this, I export them. When I export them, then I email those over to Amanda.
Kayla Kanipe: And… Amanda actually has a separate… a separate system to double-check
Kayla Kanipe: double-check that we don't already have these people engaged. She double-checks HubSpot and Contender and whatever it may be, and then she sends me back
Kayla Kanipe: She sends me back these ready-to-go outreach lists in… in HubSpot.
Kayla Kanipe: I load them all up, and I put them into a sequence.
Kayla Kanipe: The sequence is just the outright… outreach sequence. Every, like, 4 days, 5 days, they get, like, another email being like, hey, are you sure you wanna, you know, remember, talk to us, talk to Banff?
Kayla Kanipe: What we do to try to make sure that we keep everything aligned from a different bucketing perspective is create a new sequence for all of those reactive requests. So, I know that I can go in here and be like, okay.
Kayla Kanipe: Finterry sales. No one has responded, so I should probably spend more time at Finterry Sales.
Matthew smith: Holy coop.
Kayla Kanipe: in-tech CTOs, we're doing okay. Like, Kraft Uplwind, we're actually doing okay. And so it's nice, this is what I use to really kind of see and judge where I should continue spending my time.
Kayla Kanipe: And then this process is, you know, they…
Kayla Kanipe: They book on my calendar, I have the conversation, I have the conversation, a lot of my calendar is full of these chats.
Kayla Kanipe: I have all of those notes here in this database.
Kayla Kanipe: And on a weekly basis, I go in here and I tag their industry, their functional…
Kayla Kanipe: focus, you know, what they've done, add their LinkedIn, add their emails, any keywords in terms of location, their ad, all… I just tag all of these. And then we can bulk upload these into Contender.
Kayla Kanipe: And then that's where, kind of, the machine falls apart, is…
Kayla Kanipe: then it's only up to me and my brain to remember on, like, Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, the next week, since all of these people are added to Contender, to make sure that I go send Daniel to Lightspeed, and I send Will to a crew, and I send Vivek to, you know, whoever else.
Kayla Kanipe: And so that's kind of where things fall apart.
Matthew smith: You're not keeping…
Kayla Kanipe: What was that?
Matthew smith: You're not keeping track of this anywhere? Like, what you need to send off to?
Kayla Kanipe: I mean, like, I do, but also, like…
Kayla Kanipe: Because of this, like, a lot of these targetings are based on specific requests, but a lot of these people can… a lot of these people can…
Kayla Kanipe: kill a couple birds with one stone. Like…
Kayla Kanipe: Larry, we could have Blackstone, Lightspeed, OTP, like, all these people be interested in Larry, and so then it's like…
Kayla Kanipe: I need to figure out, okay, how am I prioritizing this? Do I send it to Lightspeed first?
Kayla Kanipe: next week, I don't have any… unless I just remember to send him to FTV, I won't… I won't remember that. Also, Claire, Liv, Max, David, a lot of people are talking to people, and so, like…
Kayla Kanipe: I have no idea who Chris Wood is, I don't know who Stefano is, I don't know, like…
Kayla Kanipe: you know, I want to be able to put them on things and utilize them, but I don't have that, like, visibility unless I go in here manually and be like, okay, what does Chris want to do? Then I can go add him everywhere.
Kayla Kanipe: And with more people having these conversations, and me probably taking a step away from having more of these conversations, I worry about the flow.
Matthew smith: Interesting, yeah.
km Habib: Yeah.
Matthew smith: did a lot of…
km Habib: Pretty much explain most of the part.
km Habib: Of the workflow?
km Habib: So, how do you send you whispers, like, SARS profile to 50p from over 8 weeks? How do you track who got it and when?
Kayla Kanipe: Well, usually it's all in Contender.
Kayla Kanipe: So this is, like, what a…
Kayla Kanipe: How can I… let me just type in evergreen.
Kayla Kanipe: So luckily, our side of the business, as you guys are learning, is that
Kayla Kanipe: We utilize Contender a lot more than the executive side of the business, because this platform is built for our partners.
Kayla Kanipe: And so, for example.
Kayla Kanipe: you know, evergreen CFO, all of these people will be published here, but I don't have a process for this being like, okay, I'm gonna add Larry Hellman to this pipeline.
Kayla Kanipe: And then next week, add it to, you know, another pipeline, and then the week after that, add them to another pipeline.
Kayla Kanipe: Because the last thing, we need to be smart around sectioning these out, because we can't, like…
Kayla Kanipe: you know, over-index, we can't inundate Dixit being like, hey, here are 6 introductions. Like, we do have to make sure that we space them out. And so that's the element that I don't really have flushed out.
Kayla Kanipe: And it's completely not foolproof. One thing that Amanda did do, which has been helpful, is set up…
Kayla Kanipe: these auto… Like, nudge emails, where it's like…
Kayla Kanipe: okay, you talked to Robert 3 days ago, you should publish him on, you know, your… on your first pipeline, you should publish him for New York CFOs, but then after that, there's no follow-up of, like, the next one or the next one.
Kayla Kanipe: Did that answer your questions? Is this incredibly confusing?
Matthew smith: Yeah, I mean, this is why we recorded them, so we can continue looking over them.
Matthew smith: Because there's a lot of information at once.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah, sorry.
Matthew smith: Oh, you're good.
Matthew smith: Really good snowball.
Matthew smith: Cam, do you have any more… more questions?
Matthew smith: I think he's switching over… oh, okay, he texted me. He's switching over to his main computer.
Kayla Kanipe: Okay.
Amanda Chi: Kayla, this is me thinking out loud right now. Those emails that's like, oh, you chatted with them 3 days ago, I can change this to only go on Fridays, that way it doesn't flood your inbox, like, in the middle of the week.
Amanda Chi: If we want to.
Amanda Chi: So, just putting that out there, but I just thought of that.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah, let's…
km Habib: So, do you have… do you ever have to manually check if an executive's LinkedIn is up-to-date before sending their profiles? Like, how does this work?
Kayla Kanipe: Great question, and it's a huge pain point. That's more so in Amanda's bucket in terms of her flow, but yes, that happens all the time.
Kayla Kanipe: And there's a couple things that we've done. I know that we do have… we do work with a outside partner that does update the LinkedIns,
Kayla Kanipe: Somewhat frequently, but… There's a couple problems here, and this is actually a good example, is…
Kayla Kanipe: We… how do I address this? So, one problem is Dixit. He is no longer at Credit Suisse.
Kayla Kanipe: And so we go in here and we will put
Kayla Kanipe: former CFO, Credit Suisse, and update it here. And then the auto-updater will always pick it to be, you know, whatever their most recent role is.
Kayla Kanipe: on… on LinkedIn. So, like, we don't want him to be shown as member of the board director's man group. We want him to show former CFO,
Kayla Kanipe: But, like, that auto… that auto-update just takes over. Also, the auto-update never puts former, so even if there is an end date here, it never puts former, and then our B2B partners get mad at us because they're like, oh, this isn't up-to-date, or I thought he was working there, and he isn't anymore, and so…
Kayla Kanipe: To answer your question, very long-winded, yes, we run into that problem a lot, where we have to manually check their LinkedIns.
Kayla Kanipe: Update manually and make sure that it is actually, you know, shown correctly.
Matthew smith: Okay, are you there?
Matthew smith: Yeah, it keeps logging off. Okay. Amanda, is it possible that you can walk us through, what you…
Matthew smith: kind of handle.
Matthew smith: You're in?
Amanda Chi: Yeah.
Matthew smith: Yeah.
Amanda Chi: Case.
Amanda Chi: Should I start from the top, or should I start with maybe something that takes the most amount of time, like Kayla was saying, with checking the LinkedIns and stuff like that?
Matthew smith: Yeah, start with the most painful.
Matthew smith: That takes the most time.
Amanda Chi: Okay.
Amanda Chi: Let me share my screen.
Matthew smith: Matt is just going through her… the pain point for her.
Amanda Chi: Okay, sorry, you're gonna see the whole desktop.
Amanda Chi: Don't know why it wasn't letting me do a window.
Amanda Chi: Okay, so this would be filling pipelines, but I'll actually go through the very start of this. So this would be on those calls that Kayla mentioned, we
Amanda Chi: Get these pipeline requests come in, and so…
Amanda Chi: Step one would be, okay, we're on this call with Thomas.
Amanda Chi: We took down notes, and one of our action items is the President, CMO of Consumer Digital Marketing.
Amanda Chi: I'll take that, and I'll add it to my task list, usually, like, under here, and I'll type, like.
Amanda Chi: Resident.
Amanda Chi: CMO…
Amanda Chi: then I'll do, like, LF Lingua franca, just to tell me that it… like, which client it goes under.
Amanda Chi: I'm working on it right now, and so I'll move it to in progress, and I'm here. Then I go to…
Amanda Chi: Their pipeline page, this is their team, Lingua franca.
Amanda Chi: I'll open a new pipeline, And fill out all the information here. And then hit submit.
Amanda Chi: Okay, so that's, like, we got the request, I put it on my task list, and then when I get to it, I start it.
Amanda Chi: Then, finding these ideas, this happens through Contender,
Amanda Chi: So I hit recommendations, and then…
Amanda Chi: knowing what I know about this request that we got from Thomas, I look through all the people that we have, and I… whether that's filtering with these filters, or searching their names if executives come to mind,
Amanda Chi: And this is kind of where the part of things being updated or knowing just information. So, Rebecca shows up, and Stacy shows up. I see that they're not seeking and passively seeking, but, for example, I need to know, like, is Stacy still the director and head of U.S. Sports Marketing?
Amanda Chi: So I'll go to her.
Amanda Chi: profile here.
Amanda Chi: I look and see that this is last updated October 3rd, and…
Amanda Chi: in the past, I would have been like, okay, that's great, October 3rd, that's, like.
Amanda Chi: not too long ago, she's probably still in this role, but because we've had too many incidents recently where people just update their LinkedIns, from roles they started a while ago, I'll hit sync just to make sure that
Amanda Chi: It is up to date.
Amanda Chi: Sometimes… It goes quickly, and sometimes it takes a little bit longer.
Amanda Chi: If I get tired of waiting.
Amanda Chi: Then I just click on her LinkedIn link right here.
Amanda Chi: And I double check.
Amanda Chi: And let's see. Okay, she is still the director and head of U.S. Sports Marketing.
Amanda Chi: And if I think that she's a good fit…
Amanda Chi: I'll add her to the pipeline.
km Habib: So, there's a kind of automation you have already now with LinkedIn.
km Habib: Right?
Amanda Chi: Yes, as you can see, okay, this didn't work, so I have to go and save this to PDF.
Amanda Chi: And then I'll just manually… even though I know it's up-to-date, I'll do this so that next time,
Amanda Chi: I can check the updated date and know that it's relevant.
Amanda Chi: Take an action, I'll hit Suggested.
Amanda Chi: And then here's kind of where…
Amanda Chi: Okay, Kayla, I'm just gonna tag it to you, because…
Matthew smith: Nope.
Amanda Chi: MO.
Amanda Chi: I tag it to someone on the Banff team, whoever is responsible for their relationship with Stacy, and I wait for them to approve it. So that's kind of, like, the pipeline process that takes a while. I would say the part of this where it gets stuck, though, would be actually translating
Amanda Chi: the action items from either our call notes, or we get them through an email, and putting them onto my task list, and then…
Amanda Chi: remembering I have it on my list, or seeing my list, and then getting to it In time.
Amanda Chi: For example, we just had some come in, actually, that were…
Amanda Chi: Let me find one that I just… This would be…
Amanda Chi: in making a new team, which is also another process that I do, but this…
Amanda Chi: things the same, I'll get an email from Claire, one of our advisors at BAMP, that there is another team to make, and so I'll have to just put to my task list as well. This is Richard's team.
Amanda Chi: reminding myself that I need to make this. So, I would say that's where the stickiest point is. Sometimes things live in my inbox, or things live in our call notes, and it's just not translated over into my task list, either until, like.
Amanda Chi: someone reminds me about it, or I remember it. I usually try to do it, like, right away, as soon as we're off the call, or as soon as I get the email, but…
Amanda Chi: That's not possible all the time.
km Habib: Don't answer.
Amanda Chi: That's a process with that one.
Amanda Chi: Other things that I look for… In terms of data… Quality and checking.
Amanda Chi: would be… like…
Amanda Chi: let's go back to this example, actually, is when I can add a comment. So, like, let's say Stacy.
Matthew smith: She… actually, that's not a good example, because she's a former client. I'm gonna find a current client.
Matthew smith: Okay, let's do Rebecca.
Amanda Chi: Okay.
Amanda Chi: I'm like, I think Rebecca looks relevant, I'll add her as an option.
Amanda Chi: But then I just gotta make sure…
Amanda Chi: says she's not seeking a new role, and so then I'll kind of go to… Just look through our…
Amanda Chi: client meeting notes.
Matthew smith: Sometimes I'll ask.
Amanda Chi: AI, like, is… Rebecca Burroughs.
Amanda Chi: Looking for a new role.
Amanda Chi: Or taking calls. And then I'll kind of just see if there's somewhere in the notes when they talked to Rebecca, if they mentioned.
Amanda Chi: Anything new?
Amanda Chi: Or I'll also go to HubSpot, And just kinda see…
Amanda Chi: what they talked about. I'll also do this process
Amanda Chi: let's say someone… I don't know if we're, like, warm and engaged with them, I don't know the last time that they…
Amanda Chi: spoke to us. Let me see if I can find an example, actually.
Amanda Chi: Who is one here that I'm not so confident about?
Amanda Chi: Okay, Daryl. I don't know this profile at all.
Amanda Chi: I think we know Daryl, we might not know Daryl, so I'll look and see his past
Amanda Chi: Interactions with. Okay, so we put him on two pipelines in 2024, so we… we might know him. Then I'll go to HubSpot, and I'll look and see.
Amanda Chi: Okay.
Amanda Chi: Actually, is that Daryl? I don't know if that's Daryl.
Kayla Kanipe: I don't like Randolin.
Amanda Chi: I don't think we know him either.
Amanda Chi: I'll copy his email. Okay, this Zoom box needs to move.
Matthew smith: It's a random client in there.
Amanda Chi: Yeah, okay, so I guess, you know, that's a great example of, I don't know if we know Daryl, and there's no way of knowing if we know Daryl unless I look for it manually.
Amanda Chi: Let me try to find another one. Actually, that's good to know.
Amanda Chi: Okay, Kathleen?
Kayla Kanipe: I chatted with Kathleen, but she didn't respond to me.
Amanda Chi: Okay, I guess a good example, I guess.
Amanda Chi: I don't… since I didn't talk with Kathleen, I don't know if we know Kathleen, so I'll look and find her on HubSpot, and I'll see, like, oh, okay, she talked with someone recently at Banff, like.
Amanda Chi: Decently okay to add her.
Matthew smith: Nice.
Amanda Chi: Hmm.
Amanda Chi: So yeah, it's a lot of checking our data because we have data living in so many different places. Now let's go back to this AI thing.
Amanda Chi: Okay, not actively seeking, because she just landed a role, so then I know that Rebecca's not actively seeking, and that the tag for her
Amanda Chi: Right here is correct.
Amanda Chi: But it's a lot of checking in multiple spots.
Amanda Chi: Yeah.
km Habib: That's helpful.
Amanda Chi: Hopefully.
km Habib: That's great.
Matthew smith: Trainer.
km Habib: So, how do you know which B4B partners are active or dormant? Like, which one engaged versus which one never respond? How do you know that?
Amanda Chi: That's a good question.
Amanda Chi: I'll… let me see if I can find an example.
Amanda Chi: So, if I go to someone's profile… oh, she's a 1B.
Amanda Chi: I'm gonna give…
Kayla Kanipe: Do you want to chat about, like, our, business rule of, like…
Kayla Kanipe: In the last year or something.
Amanda Chi: Yeah.
Kayla Kanipe: there's, like, an unfilitated intro. Like, we have something that categorizes them as warm, that's shown. That might be helpful here. Sorry to interrupt your flow, Amanda.
Amanda Chi: No, no, that's a good example. I'm… do you know someone?
km Habib: I'm basically trying to understand how partners exactly track… how partner tracking works, and see if health, scoring exactly exists or not, and if identify any engagement gaps.
Amanda Chi: Sorry, could you say that one more time? What would… what would be helpful to know?
km Habib: Physical understanding partner tracking.
km Habib: Then, if, health scoring exists or not.
km Habib: And…
Amanda Chi: Oh.
Amanda Chi: Okay.
Amanda Chi: I think I understand what you mean.
Amanda Chi: So if I go here, and New Recommendations, this is where I can see the most data about our clients all on Contender, our clients and just people in our network. We have this little warm tag right here, so this tells me… it's a checkbox if we are… I think I… do I have a filter?
Amanda Chi: If we are warm with them, and then it's blank if we aren't. So the business rule for this is that if their profile has been created within the last year, they're considered warm, or if we've had a facilitated intro with them.
Amanda Chi: Within the past year, I believe.
km Habib: I am.
Amanda Chi: And then these different tiers, I don't know if we actually discussed tiers, are their level of warmth with us. So, one is our executive client, like, they're currently very active with us.
Amanda Chi: 1B is former, and then 3 is this kind of, like, broader bucket that we have.
Amanda Chi: So I'll check this warm check mark to make sure that we've actually been able to talk with them in the past.
Amanda Chi: Here's a good example.
Amanda Chi: Apparently, we're warm with Brian, even though he's not a client of ours, and he's not in our, like, broader network. He was referred in by someone.
Amanda Chi: So, I'll go to his profile, and I'll see, like, why are we warm with him? Also, because his profile was made a long time ago, so it doesn't meet that business rule of the one-year mark.
Amanda Chi: I'll go to his past information performance with us.
Amanda Chi: It says an intro completed in 2023.
Amanda Chi: But then I'll also just check, because that was, like, 2 years ago, I'll check HubSpot to see…
Amanda Chi: what that facilitated intro was like.
Amanda Chi: If we have email communications with him recently.
Amanda Chi: Okay, so it looks like June 2024 was when we reached out to him again, but he didn't respond, so I'll actually consider this
Amanda Chi: not necessarily warm, because I don't know, or I don't feel confident that we could even reach him again.
Amanda Chi: So even though he has that little… Zoom going.
Amanda Chi: Even though he has that checkbox that says warm, I still need to do some data quality.
Amanda Chi: Checking to make sure that I can actually trust this.
km Habib: Okay.
km Habib: Got it.
Amanda Chi: Does that make… does that answer your question?
km Habib: There's answer the questions.
km Habib: My next question to Yamander is, have you ever talked to Jessica or Evgeny about, content needing an API? Is that on their roadmap?
Kayla Kanipe: I don't think that there'.
Amanda Chi: I know the words in English, but I don't know what those mean. You just said…
km Habib: I think that's Oh, I'm sorry. I think Jessica is from your Foolish tech engineer.
Amanda Chi: Yes.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah, I don't think that there's any plans on the roadmap for an AP, to be… to build Contender to be API compatible. Was that your question?
km Habib: Yep, yep, that's okay.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah. It… yeah, it's too…
Kayla Kanipe: It would be a whole, like, revamp. It's been in conversations for years, but it's… it's… it's not feasible at this point.
km Habib: Okay, so mostly we need to work with the retool in this case, right?
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah. Yeah, I think this goes back to, like, what I was saying on Friday of being, like, I think our problem here is that, or at least, you know, on our side, a problem that we're gonna run into is that commun… or that contender doesn't necessarily like communicating with many other
Kayla Kanipe: platforms because of the lack of API, capability, and so we use Retool as that middleman a lot.
km Habib: Yeah.
km Habib: Container…
Matthew smith: Facts this morning.
Kayla Kanipe: Hmm?
Matthew smith: That's what we discussed with Max, that a lot of the problems that you guys are having right now stems from Contender not having API.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah.
km Habib: So, Keller, a question to you. If I could… if I could build you one automation this week, what would make your life easier? Like, what would it be?
Kayla Kanipe: That is a great question.
Kayla Kanipe: And I think I go back and forth. It would be either, like, something for me with that second half of the…
Kayla Kanipe: broader network growth, visibility, machine, whatever it is, like, after I get someone more… like, after I have the call, everything that kind of comes
Kayla Kanipe: after that, that would be extremely helpful. But also, you know, I want to be mindful of Amanda's workflows, too. But I think from literally my workflow, that would be the most helpful.
Matthew smith: comfortable.
Amanda Chi: That's like kidding in a candy shop.
Amanda Chi: I could build you anything, what would you like?
Kayla Kanipe: And maybe it's top of mind right now, but I think it's gonna be most impactful, especially going into the new year. And we're gonna have to really depend on… on that.
Amanda Chi: So I would say a lot of our operations right now and ability to provide impact to our clients relies on our memory to remember people we just chatted with in the network, or remember people that other people have chatted with.
Amanda Chi: Or remember even tasks, and what we just last talked about on…
Amanda Chi: a call 2 months ago, and it's relevant now. So working past, like, getting… or yeah, working on our knowledge barriers, like.
Amanda Chi: If you forget something, it doesn't live anywhere else, or it's not easily surfaceable, because our platforms aren't talking to each other, then that's kind of just gone into
Amanda Chi: Like, the abyss, until you remember and pull it back out again.
km Habib: Yeah.
km Habib: Got most of the answers. Thank you.
km Habib: Caroline, I wonder.
km Habib: Rest will get figured out after seeing the backend of HubSpot, Ritual, and Notions.
km Habib: So, we're now easily waiting for the credentials, to,
km Habib: Take… to look out all the status.
km Habib: This will give us a better,
km Habib: A look on what we can do better to automate multiple, a manual process.
Amanda Chi: Yeah, actually, I sent over an invitation to access HubSpot.
Amanda Chi: This morning, so let me know if you weren't able to get.
km Habib: Yeah, I…
Amanda Chi: And also let me know what permissions you need. I gave you the sales professional seat, which is what
Amanda Chi: Kayla, myself, David and Claire and Liv all have.
Amanda Chi: But if you need more access, let me know.
km Habib: Yeah, sure, sure. We'll let you know in the Slack.
Matthew smith: And then also Notion would be extremely helpful, because that's a lot… that's where a lot of your documentation lives, if I'm not mistaken.
Amanda Chi: Yes. I've asked our, our tech team, or sorry, not tech, but, like, IT team, Interlace, to give you access. I think they're working on that right now.
Amanda Chi: And I also did see your request for information about Contender. I don't know if you saw my response with some questions to that, too.
Matthew smith: Yeah, I responded to that earlier. Let me see.
Amanda Chi: Oh, okay, great, I'll pass… I'll pass it along to our tech team.
Amanda Chi: Yeah, for Notion, I guess… There's a lot that we do in Notion.
Amanda Chi: I don't know if we covered the gist of it.
Matthew smith: What else?
Matthew smith: Yeah.
Kayla Kanipe: I mean, in Notion, I pretty much mainly live in…
Kayla Kanipe: I live in tasks, I live in…
Kayla Kanipe: tier, like, network growth notes, as well as, enterprise notes. That's where I spend most of my time in Notion.
Matthew smith: But maybe…
Kayla Kanipe: Whoop.
Matthew smith: What about your communication in Slack? I see you have, like, 200-some… messages in Slack.
Kayla Kanipe: Oh, see that.
Matthew smith: Oh, no, Max is familiar.
Kayla Kanipe: What do you mean, 200 met? I mean, I would say Slack communication is just, like, day-to-day internal, like, Amanda and I are back and forth.
Kayla Kanipe: just, like, oh, let's update on this or that, or do you want to add this person, or this, or have you talked to this person? It's really just kind of, like, quick tactical messages across the org.
Matthew smith: So no clients live on Slack.
Matthew smith: Right.
Kayla Kanipe: I… we technically have… two, three, two and a half-ish clients on Slack, but, like.
Kayla Kanipe: Communication is very far few between with them through Slack.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Matthew smith: Awesome, just wanna make sure.
Matthew smith: Cool, yeah, so we just need the rest of that access, and then I think we're solid here.
Matthew smith: If you can share the recordings of this call, that'd be great. We can kind of review it and continue to go through it throughout the week.
Matthew smith: But yeah, like Habib said, we can just flush everything out this week, and then kind of prepare the… what we think is going to be the best…
Matthew smith: Course of action, come Friday.
Matthew smith: And then we'll start building out everything.
Matthew smith: Cool, love it.
Amanda Chi: I'm actually… Oh, sorry.
Kayla Kanipe: I was just gonna ask if you guys still need your time tomorrow, or if you got everything that you needed, or… and Amanda, you showed everything that you wanted to.
Amanda Chi: That was kind of my point. I was wondering, Matthew, have you seen Retool yet? Like, the dashboards that Kayla and I use most often?
Matthew smith: No, actually, I haven't. Oh, that would be great.
Amanda Chi: Maybe, Kayla, do you want to show them how you grab all the information you need to prepare for a call?
Amanda Chi: Beforehand? Because that's, like, a retool Notion crossover.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah.
Kayla Kanipe: So this is our… the B2B,
Kayla Kanipe: just enterprise services, like, our dashboard that has all of our information here. So, pretty much what I do is, this houses…
Kayla Kanipe: Just quick stats. Are you gonna do something?
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah, quick stats…
Kayla Kanipe: what intros were facilitated, you know, which ones are pending, just intro requests, who has been viewed, who have we submitted, where are comments, who is marked not interesting. It's really just a snapshot all across the board.
Kayla Kanipe: And so, let's just say, you know, live action, we're gonna be connecting with
Kayla Kanipe: Rachel at Blue Dot tomorrow, so I'll go in here and type in Blue Dot Capital.
Kayla Kanipe: I'll go here and be like, oh, what was our last conversation with Rachel and Blue Dot?
Kayla Kanipe: kind of take a look at the notes, have we done all of this? You know, refresh, yada yada. And then I look, and I say, okay, the last time that we connected with Blue Dot was…
Kayla Kanipe: November 3rd. So what activity has happened since November 3rd?
Kayla Kanipe: Alright, so we've introduced him to Jonathan Guido and David Joseph, so then I will, like, literally open a…
Kayla Kanipe: another… Enterprise server, or, like, call notes.
Kayla Kanipe: And, like, prep with this accordingly, and be like, recent intros…
Matthew smith: Okay, come on. Okay.
Kayla Kanipe: recent intros, and then literally copy and paste all of those, and then be like, oh, was there anything else that we need to reference?
Kayla Kanipe: How was Money 2020? You know?
Kayla Kanipe: Peter Renton, just kind of, like, make sure that we're following up on things from last time. But that's what I do, I kind of use this
Kayla Kanipe: And then copy-paste, and just use that as, like, a… you know, as a baseline.
Kayla Kanipe: I also use this a lot for that intro policing, what I was telling you that I spend time on, is I go through here, and I'm like, alright, who are all of the people that,
Kayla Kanipe: Hasn't been… interest hasn't been facilitated, and then just, like, go down the list.
Kayla Kanipe: And then check in on every single one. Like.
Kayla Kanipe: Why isn't Sky Kelly been intro'd? Why hasn't John? Why isn't this? Why isn't that?
Matthew smith: Okay, and I remember one of the main problems you had was with tagging and retool, is that correct?
Kayla Kanipe: Not tagging in retool, tagging in Notion.
Matthew smith: It's just time consuming.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Kayla Kanipe: And that's mainly for… This stuff that's time-consuming.
Kayla Kanipe: So, like, I don't know if there's a way, because we have Zoom on, like, we have Zoom…
Kayla Kanipe: Transcribers on, or recordings, like…
Kayla Kanipe: there was a way to kind of, like, zoom figure out what these buckets are? I… I don't know. Again, who am I to make solutions here, but…
Matthew smith: Yeah, we have to just filter it through, filter all the data coming through from Zoom.
Kayla Kanipe: Yeah.
Matthew smith: Cool, and then Amanda, what about you? Do you handle anything in Retool?
Amanda Chi: Yes, I do. Show you.
Amanda Chi: Okay, this is our homepage for Retool. Where I live, I have, like, my own tasks, like we mentioned,
Amanda Chi: A lot of it is… okay, let's go… let's do Impact Tracker.
Amanda Chi: So this is where we track things that come in.
Amanda Chi: successes and wins from our clients, so we either hear about it on a call, or something comes in over email. I add it to this database.
Amanda Chi: And so, just, like, new, item…
Amanda Chi: fill this out, I'll tag it to a user, on our B4B side, and then I'll put down, just a blurb of what
Amanda Chi: the impact thing is. Tag it to a specific category here.
Amanda Chi: I'll tag the date that we heard about this.
Amanda Chi: And then, if it's related to an executive client, I'll tag them here. And if it's related to an active B4B client.
Amanda Chi: I'll tag it there.
Amanda Chi: And so, this is… where I live, it's a lot of manual tagging. If something comes in
Amanda Chi: over email that either David doesn't forward to me, or I don't catch it in my email, because it's…
Amanda Chi: It got buried, or something like that, then it…
Amanda Chi: doesn't make it in. If Kayla's on a call and I'm not on the call, and there's a win, and I don't see it in the notes, then that also doesn't get pulled into here.
Amanda Chi: So, that's one.
Amanda Chi: Area of impact tracking.
Amanda Chi: Another one is our manual trackers, so we have these trackers with Evercore… And this is checking introductions.
Amanda Chi: This is shared externally with our Epicor team, and so, I update it here, and then it's synced to a different page,
Amanda Chi: And they can view that there.
Amanda Chi: I don't know why it's not… it's loading funny.
Amanda Chi: So I hit View Site, this is the page that…
Amanda Chi: The Evercore team has access to, and so whatever updates I make on my end, they see it on theirs.
Amanda Chi: And this is just how we've decided to track introductions for them.
Amanda Chi: So it looks exactly the same.
Amanda Chi: Another area where I live in Retool…
Amanda Chi: So, my responsibility for our Tier 2 through 5 Notes.
Amanda Chi: Kayla, Liv, Max, anyone who's talking with these clients will fill out those notes and tag it appropriately, like the industry and their function tag.
Amanda Chi: What I do, then, is at the end of every week,
Amanda Chi: It will populate into this Ready for Review.
Amanda Chi: View.
Amanda Chi: Sorry, my computer is going a little bit slowly right now, too.
Amanda Chi: Aye.
Matthew smith: Very good.
Matthew smith: Must be something in the air today.
Amanda Chi: Okay, so this is what it looks like when it's kind of all messed up, before people have had a chance to go and tag things correctly. When it's ready for import, though, the notes will pop into
Amanda Chi: Is ready for import view.
Matthew smith: I'll then go here…
Amanda Chi: and export it, all the information, and then I'll go to Contender, and this is when we upload profiles.
Amanda Chi: And I'll hit New.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Amanda Chi: bulk import executives.
Amanda Chi: And then I'll select a file, the file I just downloaded from Notion, click and drag it into here, and then, Contender will parse information, and then automatically create the profiles, and then send me an email confirming it's done, and if there's any errors, it will flag those for me.
Amanda Chi: So…
Amanda Chi: that, I guess, is a roadblocker, would just be waiting to get all the notes in from people, and then uploading them. I do it every Friday, and that's just kind of the cadence we've set.
Amanda Chi: Sometimes if we need a profile sooner, then we'll just manually make it throughout the week. If Kayla talks to someone and she's like, this guy needs to go on this pipeline right away, she'll just make their profile herself.
Amanda Chi: Yeah, that's another page that I live in Notion.
Amanda Chi: And… I think that might be it for Notion.
Amanda Chi: I can go over Zapier and Whale Sync if you want to right now, as well.
Matthew smith: Yes, let's do that.
Matthew smith: Okay.
Amanda Chi: Let me walk through the process of how we create a client.
Amanda Chi: in Notion, because that… I don't… did not… actually, did Max already do this with you?
Matthew smith: Let me see, I think he did, yes.
Amanda Chi: Okay, oh yes, he did it on the call. But I'll show you what Whalesync looks like.
Amanda Chi: Just to let you know.
Amanda Chi: as well.
Amanda Chi: And I know Will Sync wasn't part of the original things you requested access to, so let me know if you need access to this.
Amanda Chi: Yes.
km Habib: Yes, we need, we need to access this whole thing.
Amanda Chi: Okay. I will invite you then. So this is connection between HubSpot and Notion.
Amanda Chi: And…
Amanda Chi: we've mapped these things to be synced across, so that's why Max only needs to put in the candidate tier and the advisor into HubSpot and not into Notion, because it will automatically sync.
Amanda Chi: Huh.
Amanda Chi: So these are the mappings that we have.
km Habib: Do you also handle the Japier automation, Amanda?
Amanda Chi: This was set up by our former CTO, and so I'm just in charge of
Amanda Chi: managing it if it breaks, or if I get error messages.
km Habib: Okay.
Amanda Chi: Yeah, we haven't set up any… I don't… I don't know what processes,
Amanda Chi: Or, like, I guess what else Whale Sync can do?
Amanda Chi: So I don't know if there's other things that we could set up with it, too, but I know that this is one that we have for specifically HubSpot to Notion.
Amanda Chi: I can show you Typeform as well, actually.
Amanda Chi: This type form goes into… A background deep dive.
Amanda Chi: Into here.
Matthew smith: into here?
Amanda Chi: Okay, so under the Client Ops page, and actually, Typeform also has our feedback from our events.
Amanda Chi: So, background deep dive, this form. We send it to our clients when they're… I'll get up results.
Amanda Chi: the results from here… oh, this is me testing it, because it would break, so I had to fix it again.
Amanda Chi: And then they get pulled into this database here in Notion.
Amanda Chi: Responses to the questions that we've asked them.
Amanda Chi: And that's through the Typeform to Notion integration that's available on Typeform.
Amanda Chi: I think it's under here.
Amanda Chi: Yep, turned on.
Amanda Chi: That's another integration we have.
Amanda Chi: Yeah, the last integration we have is Zapier, or, like, Sync, I guess.
Amanda Chi: And this is what it looks like.
Amanda Chi: So, we have…
Amanda Chi: a couple different things going on. One is, like, a Zoom summary and a Zoom transcript getting pulled into…
Amanda Chi: Our client meeting notes page, so…
Amanda Chi: when David, Liv, Claire, Max, or Lily are on a call.
Amanda Chi: from Zoom will automatically get pulled into Notion.
Amanda Chi: Literally every single word that they said. And then, same thing with a summary.
Amanda Chi: As well.
Amanda Chi: And this is so that things live in Notion and not just, like, in our emails.
Amanda Chi: This would be where tagging is also, appropriate, because we need to make sure that it's tagged to a client, and then also the type of call that they have.
Amanda Chi: Let's talk to a client.
Amanda Chi: So, I guess here's an example of, like, this transcript got uploaded,
Amanda Chi: I think it's Kathleen DeRose? Yep, it is. So then we would need to tag.
Amanda Chi: her here.
Amanda Chi: As a client. And then same thing here.
Amanda Chi: So that's, like, the manual part of this.
Amanda Chi: And I believe this is a…
Amanda Chi: check and call? Actually, I'm not sure if it's a check and call or not, but if it was.
Amanda Chi: Then we would tag it here under a check-in call for call type, or whatever else the call was for.
Amanda Chi: So that's one version of Zoom summary, Zoom Transcript getting pulled into
Amanda Chi: Notion, another one is, have searches in the market.
Amanda Chi: And so, this page…
Amanda Chi: Anytime an executive tells us about a search that either they were called for, or one that they heard about in the market, just because we want to collect as much insight from the market as possible, we forward it to an email distribution
Amanda Chi: address called Active Searches. Let me see if I can pull up some examples for you.
Amanda Chi: Here.
Amanda Chi: So, it'll look like… This one?
Amanda Chi: We format it like this, so…
Amanda Chi: Nicole Carroll got called about, had a small business card at U.S. Bank, so David sends it to this Active Search's email.
Amanda Chi: our Zapier extracts search info from email, runs, and then it pulls it into this database here.
Amanda Chi: Where it says Nicole Carroll, US Bank.
Amanda Chi: large, what the role title was, and then through AI, tells us what
Amanda Chi: what else was available, or information? And then we have to manually tag it to Nicole Carroll here.
Amanda Chi: So that's another manual part. I don't know…
Amanda Chi: Let me see… Bobby Morris. This is the part where I have to double check.
Amanda Chi: Okay, Bobby Morrison is a client, and he did get called.
Amanda Chi: Then someone we need to go here. I don't know if he's been made yet.
Amanda Chi: You might not have his profile made yet.
Amanda Chi: Okay, yeah, it's not made, so we can't tag it to him yet, we have to wait on that.
Amanda Chi: But if there is a client
Amanda Chi: Wow, they did a good job at tagging already. But there's a client that's not tagged yet, we'll re-tag them here.
Amanda Chi: So that is how we primarily use Zapier.
Amanda Chi: Oh, there's one more that David has, actually.
Amanda Chi: My emails… if David… David has his app set up,
Amanda Chi: I think it's this one, organized Gmail, emails, and Notion. If he has an email come through that a client has asked for some information or insight, and he was able to help them well and respond well.
Amanda Chi: he'll start it as, like, a favorite email, and then it gets pulled into here so that everyone else can see his response. To help us with our responses to clients, if there's a similar request that comes along.
Amanda Chi: So yeah. And it just includes, like, the entire email.
Amanda Chi: It just populates all into here.
Amanda Chi: Yeah, and it just lives in this tracker.
Amanda Chi: it is a little bit of a mess, because this can cross a variety of different ways. He provided impact, or different smart things that were said.
Amanda Chi: But…
Amanda Chi: the goal was to get it out of inboxes, because we can't search each other's inboxes, and into Notion, because then we could ask Notion AI, and hopefully it would get flagged somewhere.
Matthew smith: Hmm. Okay.
Amanda Chi: I think that is everything.
Amanda Chi: Thank you, boys.
Amanda Chi: I know that's a lot.
km Habib: Yeah, I think you have covered almost all of this.
km Habib: But for technical purposes, I think I have missed few. I will review that video.
Amanda Chi: Okay.
km Habib: Or better.
km Habib: So, do you have any, let's say, priority-based, any, lists to make automation?
Matthew smith: Of any system.
Matthew smith: operating system.
km Habib: In a specific… if you have…
Amanda Chi: I think for me, because my work is very tactical.
Amanda Chi: What would help me the most would be those, like, automated Setting up tasks, basically.
km Habib: Okay.
Amanda Chi: So I think there's… like, setting up an individual task doesn't take that much time, but if it gets missed.
Amanda Chi: through an email, or through a client call, or some note, or some Slack somewhere.
Amanda Chi: and I just don't see it, then…
Amanda Chi: that's not good. Or if it comes to my attention later, and then there's a crazy rush to get it done, I think that would be really helpful, being able to pull out
Amanda Chi: tasks, or also, I guess, with that, like, pieces of feedback and information that I need to go track somewhere else. I understand that sometimes tracking will be manual, and I'll have to do that, but it would be great if something… tech could help me identify those pieces.
Amanda Chi: To then go track.
km Habib: Sure. Basically, AI can help, in this case, to categorize or to classify the information as you exactly want.
km Habib: That's great.
Amanda Chi: Hmm.
km Habib: Yeah, me too.
Matthew smith: Awesome.
Matthew smith: Well, we have our work cut out for us, so… Thank you, Matt.
Matthew smith: Yup.
Amanda Chi: Of course.
Matthew smith: Yes, everything follows.
Matthew smith: We should have a report back to you guys, shortly, especially once we get the access to… sorry.
Matthew smith: Once we get access to the tech.
Matthew smith: Okay. So…
Amanda Chi: You need access to…
Amanda Chi: What else? So, I have Interlaced working on Notion and Retool and Google Suite Access, because I don't have the ability to grant you guys access to those right now.
Amanda Chi: Other things you need would be Zapier.
km Habib: Will sync. JPR will sing, yeah.
Amanda Chi: Okay, those two.
Matthew smith: I think we're… and then maybe Zoom for the transcript, because if we're using Zapier, you have to log into Zoom, but…
Matthew smith: I'm not 100% sure if we'll need that.
Amanda Chi: With Zapier.
Amanda Chi: Because of how I've been setting up everyone else, since it's their personal Zoom accounts, I have to hop on a call with, like, Max, for example, and have him log into his Zoom. I can't do it for him.
Matthew smith: There's okay, fine, we can.
Matthew smith: We'll hold off on that for now, then.
Amanda Chi: Okay.
km Habib: Alright, I will look into getting you guys access to Zapier and Wheelsync.
Amanda Chi: Thank you.
Matthew smith: Awesome. Thanks, Amanda. Enjoy the rest of your day.
km Habib: Do you want to…
Amanda Chi: You too. Bye.